{
    "id": "a1cee98e33394db3b5167508362f0ac8",
    "title": "Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He showed me a photo. / I ...................................... a photo by him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had shown",
                "was shown",
                "have shown"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This box contains chocolates. / Chocolates ............................... in this box.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are containing",
                "are contained",
                "have contained"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who does not hate liars? / By whom ............................. liars not hated?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "have",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Solve this problem. / Let this problem .............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is solved",
                "be solved",
                "has solved"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I expect you to do the work. / You .................................... to do this work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expected",
                "are expected",
                "have expected"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His conduct shocked his mother. / His mother .................................. by his conduct.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shocked",
                "was shocked",
                "had shocked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He could do nothing. / Nothing .................................... by him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can be done",
                "could done",
                "could be done"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know this gentleman? / Is this gentleman ............................... to you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "known"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not tease the animals. / Let the animals not ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "be teasing",
                "teased",
                "be teased"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Lower the price. /Let the price ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "be lower",
                "be lowered",
                "is lowered"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}